efluxmedia.com 2009-10-20

# EfluxMedia News - Privacy Policy

Collection of your Personal Information 

eFluxMedia will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before ordering e-mail newsletters, joining the site, becoming a subscriber, signing up for an event, or when purchasing and/or registering to use eFluxMedia services or products. Personal information collected by eFluxMedia is often limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. 

eFluxMedia collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to improve the relevance of content, and to provide statistics regarding use of eFluxMedia.

eFluxMedia also collects information about which pages our customers visit within the site. This site usage data is never linked with personal information unless a user consents as described below.

eFluxMedia uses its own membership and subscription system. When you sign in to this site using this system, you will be asked to provide your login and a password to sign you in. 

How we use your Personal Information

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

* To ensure our site content is relevant to your needs and interests.  
* To deliver services, such as updates, newsletters, pre-delivered content, that you request, subscribe to or purchase.  
* To allow you access to restricted areas of our site as appropriate.   

We will merge site-usage data with anonymous demographic information for research and marketing purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide content that is more relevant. In some restricted sections of eFluxMedia, with your approval, we will combine site-visitation data with your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content. If you decline permission, we will not provide you the personalized service and won't merge your personal information with site usage data.

eFluxMedia may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

(a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on eFluxMedia or the site;  
(b) protect and defend the rights or property of eFluxMedia, or  
(c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of eFluxMedia employees, users, or members of the public.

Control of your Personal Information

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, eFluxMedia will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.  
Registering also allows you to tell us how or whether you want eFluxMedia to communicate with you. After registering, go to your personal homepage and establish your preferences in the Options sections. There, you can decide what information you want to receive and how you want to receive it. Or you can tell us not to contact you by selecting the appropriate option.  
eFluxMedia occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services. If you want to receive these offers, you should check the box in the Options section of your profile or indicate it upon registering.

eFluxMedia may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical or service issues related to the site or a service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the site operation and are needed in order that we comply with etiquette regarding newsletter conformation and other practices.

Accessing your Personal Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current, as well as the ability to remove information stored by us about you.  

If you register on eFluxMedia or subscribe to a newsletter, you can review and edit your personal information on your profile. You will be asked to enter your login and password before viewing your personal information, unless you have chosen for the site to remember your details. You can also be removed from any Newsletter by clicking the unsubscribe link which is present in every one.

In your Profile you can:

* View and edit personal information you have already given us  
* Tell us whether you want eFluxMedia to send you marketing information.  
* Choose whether you want third parties to send you their offers by postal mail or receive e-mail via eFluxMedia from these companies.  
* Subscribe, or cancel subscriptions, to newsletters about our services or content.  
* Choose which Items you are tracking.

Some services and features offered on eFluxMedia may collect information that is not accessible via your Profile. However, in such cases, you can access your personal information by contacting eFluxMedia as described at the bottom of this statement.

Security of your Personal Information

eFluxMedia is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Children's Personal Information

eFluxMedia is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13 years old.

Protecting Children

eFluxMedia is committed to protecting children from any content inappropriate for them to view or from anything which their parents do not want them to see. We also endeavor to stop children under 13 from accessing certain parts of the site by requiring confirmation of age.

The site is aimed at a general audience and has a strict policy against obscenity, racism, bigotry or sexism. However, it does review media and arts which cover a broad spectrum of subjects and have a variety of ratings. So we feel there is some content not appropriate for children under 13 years old. 

We cannot accept any responsibility for persons accessing parts of the site against the wishes of their parents where we have been given false information. If you are concerned about anything you see on the site please do not hesitate to contact us. We can also provide some limited advice on protecting your children from inappropriate content.

Use of Cookies

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on your computer or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above.

We also use cookies to collect information on which newsletter links are clicked by customers. This information is used to ensure we are sending information customers want to read and so improve the service. It is collected in aggregate form and never linked with your personal information.

We also uses cookies in connection with our membership and subscriber services.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the eFluxMediaWeb site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to access the full services and content on the site.

Changes to this Statement   

eFluxMedia will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, eFluxMedia will notify you by placing a prominent notice on the Web site.
